<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Pikmin</string>

    <string name="titulo_toolbar">Pikmin</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">About</string>
    <string name="ajustes">Settings</string>

    <!-- String para el titulo de toolbar en ajustes-->
    <string name="toolbar_ajustes">Settings</string>

    <!-- String para el titulo de toolbar en detalles-->
    <string name="toolbar_pantalla_detalles">Details Pikmin</string>

    <string name="nombre_pikmin">Name</string>
    <string name="pikmin_rojo">Red Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_amarillo">Yellow Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_azul">Blue Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_blanco">White Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_morado">Purple Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_petreo">Rock Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_alado">Winged Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_gelido_ice">Ice Pikmin</string>
    <string name="pikmin_luminoso_glow">Glow Pikmin</string>
    <string name="snackbar"> ¡Welcome to the world of Pikmin!</string>
    <!-- Toast ajustes -->
    <string name="toast_ajustes">You have pressed</string>
    <!-- Toast pantalla detalles -->
    <string name="toast_detalles">You have selected the Pikmin:</string>
    <!-- String para el cuadro de dialogo acerca de y version  -->
    <!-- String para el cuadro de dialogo acerca de y version  -->
    <string name="acerca_de_dialogo">About...</string>
    <string name="app_desarrollada_dialogo">Application developed by [Abraham C]. Version 1.0 >> Lie.. version 30.1 at least.. and I sometimes watch Pikmin</string>
    <string name="salir_dialogo">Accept</string>
    <!-- String toast modo oscuro pantalla ajustes -->
    <string name="modo_activado"> Dark mode on</string>
    <string name="modo_desactivado"> Dark mode off</string>

    <!-- String toast cambio idioma  pantalla ajustes -->
    <string name="idioma_es">Languaje Spanish</string>
    <string name="idioma_en">Languaje English </string>

    <string name="titulo_descripcion_detalle">Detail</string>
    <string name="titulo_habilidad_detalle">Abilities</string>
    <string name="descripcion_detalle">Description details</string>
    <string name="habilidades_detalle">Abilities details</string>
    <string name="pikmin_rojo_detalle">
        Red Pikmin are characterized by their scarlet bodies and pointed noses.
        In addition to the plant-like traits of their species, they have animal characteristics
        such as a strong fighting spirit and a high degree of curiosity.
        They have great adaptability, as they are not only resistant to extreme heat,
        but also inhabit a wide variety of ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_rojo_habilidades">
        Fire immunity, high offensive capability.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_amarillo_detalle">
        They are characterized by their yellow bodies and a pair of ear-like lamellae that
        allow them to dig quickly and reach great heights when thrown. Another distinguishing trait
        is their bodies ability to conduct electricity. They are not only resistant to it,
        but seem to enjoy it.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_amarillo_habilidades">
        Electricity resistance, High flight ability, Excellent diggers
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_azul_detalle">
        They are characterized by their blue bodies and inscrutable facial expressions. Unlike most
        other rambulatory species, which cannot breathe underwater, Blue Pikmin have gills
        that resemble a mouth. These gills allow them to survive in both aquatic and terrestrial ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_azul_habilidades">
        Underwater breathing, Excellent swimmers
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_blanco_detalle">
        They are characterized by their white bodies and red eyes. Their small bodies secrete a potent venom,
        which makes them immune to certain poisons. White Pikmin seeds can be obtained
        through ivory bouncing sprouts that only grow in underground regions.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_blanco_habilidades">
        Poison immunity, Venomous bodies, Speed
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_morado_detalle">
        They are characterized by their robust and strong bodies. They are bigger and stronger than the rest of their species.
        They weigh 10 times more than any other Pikmin. Like White Pikmin, they can only be born from
        bouncing sprouts found exclusively in underground regions, making them a unique species.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_morado_habilidades">
        Weight, Great carrying capacity, Born underground
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_petreo_detalle">
        They are a parasitic type of Pikmin called "Ermikmin" that takes a stone as a host, and similar to a seed
        rooting through rock cracks, the Pikmin’s roots penetrate the stone.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_petreo_habilidades">
        Unbreakable, Sturdy, Non-adhesive
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_alado_detalle">
        They are characterized by their pink bodies and prominent blue eyes that look like lenses.
        They move gracefully through the air with their wings, but their attacks do not deal much damage.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_alado_habilidades">
        Flight ability, Weak attacks
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_gelido_detalle">
        They belong to a parasitic subtype of Pikmin called "Ermikmin". They obtain and maintain their bodies
        through a process that constantly generates new ice from ambient moisture using their low-temperature core.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_gelido_habilidades">
        Freezing properties, Cold immunity
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_luminoso_detalle">
        They are characterized by their radiant green bodies. When the leaf on their head blooms,
        it takes the shape of a star. They have several traits that distinguish them from other Pikmin types,
        one being that instead of sprouting from onions, they sprout from lumilomas which only appear at night and in underground regions.
    </string>
    <string name="pikmin_luminoso_habilidades">
        No feet and float in the air. Immune to many elements that affect other Pikmin types,
        Active at night and underground, Unusual behavior.
    </string>

    <!-- Strings for activity_main_ajustes layout -->
    <string name="modo">Theme</string>
    <string name="idioma">Language</string>
    <string name="descripcion_dia">Day Mode</string>
    <string name="descripcion_noche">Night Mode</string>
</resources>